Hello everyone!
I am on my way to lunch with Yulian and Jannie and we're getting fish
cheeks as usual.
I feel like we always go to like the same two places.
They're gonna be a little late I think I'm gonna go to the street over
and get some matcha.
It's called matcha because the line is very short So I'm gonna take advantage
I'm so excited!
We just finished eating and now we're gonna go get Mimi's That's for us Mimi's
for Mimi No swag gap but age gap of two years Oh god We're going
to the World Cup!
Get it on!
That's amazing Yeah
We are on our way to the World Cup Oh my voice
My voice is kind of gone right now But we are on the way to
the World Cup We are watching France vs Sweden
I'm so nervous
It's so good
We're picking up blair salsa man's dress shirts for his tux
And I just decided to tag along because I have been cooped up at home
For several weeks and I just need To get out
The best thing about Korea is that the food is delicious.
I'm going to go to a cafe.
Hello everyone!
We're going on a date!
We got invited to a coconut dinner because they're having a collab with a Korean
Michelin restaurant.
So we're gonna go and enjoy the food today.
We're starving.
Ray and Jannie are also invited so we're excited to see them as well but
it is a true New York summer.
Everyone is out.
You ate all the squid already.
This is casual.
I'm handsome
And then my workout closed because I'm about to do a quick little workout I'm
counting down the days till my wedding The last month is when everything just becomes
chaos.
It's been pretty busy for the most part, but there's one thing that has changed
the game for me.
And that is my home gym.
I've been so locked in on my workouts ever since I got my Gym Monster
2 by Speedience.
It makes working out really easy.
It saves me so much time.
I don't have to commute to the gym.
My fiance and I loved it so much, we actually canceled our gym membership because
it literally has everything we need in this compact smart gym.
And what I love most about it is that it's extremely space-saving.
This is my office and I don't have an extra room for a dedicated gym.
So this is great because it takes up no space.
My fiance loves to work out and he didn't think that this could actually replace
going to a real gym.
After using it, he is so impressed.
So it comes fully assembled in one package.
So it's really easy to install and I can do all types of workout.
I can do cardio on a rowing machine, then jump right into Pilates or string
training, depending on my mood.
They have a library of free workout classes or you can live freely if you
prefer to do your own workouts.
The cable heights and positions can be easily adjusted so you can do different types
of workouts.
And it also comes with this Bluetooth smart ring which you can use to adjust
the weights.
Obviously you can use this screen as well, but if you're like working out you
can just easily move like this.
And it also tracks your left and right balance in real time so you can
see if you're lifting evenly which is really helpful.
I feel like it was made very intentionally.
It has really cool and useful features like the eccentric mode that can be used
to get the most effective workout results It also has a spotter mode to make
lifting safe and secure and all of your personal profile and metrics are all Intelligently
collected and can be synced to Strava
And that completes my workout, I love my upgraded home gym if you're interested in
the gym monster, too I will leave a link in the description and you can
use my code Michelle for $90 off.
I need to wash up now
Happy Saturday everyone!
I am at Beverly Hills Rejuvenation Center getting some laser touch-ups I have some
hyperpigmentation, some sunspots that I want to get removed At least fade a little bit
before the wedding Of course, my scar that's never fading and some moles that I
have on my back
You like wet sunscreen?
Have you tried it?
I don't know hello everyone i just woke up so I'm
really puffy today is my last hair appointment before my weddings I have been playing
around with all sorts of foundations as you can see I have this and I
have this I think I broke out like 6 times in the past month such
terrible timing I do have a makeup artist I was actually contemplating whether or not
I should do my own.
And with foundation, I just love Clé de Peau.
Like whenever I wear Clé de Peau, my skin is just more radiant and it
also gives me the coverage that I need.
And it's also a summer wedding so I need to consider that it's gonna be
hot and humid.
These are the two foundations that I'm going back and forth from.
Favorite foundation, this is called The Foundation by Clé de Peau.
The most beautiful coverage and finish.
Anytime I wear this, I always get compliments on how good my skin looks.
This one is the Radiant Fluid Foundation Matte.
I'm not usually a matte foundation girly, but for longevity for my wedding day, I
feel like matte might be the way to go.
So I'm just testing this out every chance I can get.
I'm gonna use the Yoonjuff Skin Prep.
and then take one of these sponges and I blend it out
on my way
to the session to get my haircut and color by Mariko Nicole and James are
actually gonna come later for their haircut appointment and they'll probably get something to eat
after and then later tonight I am going to BTS
It's
nice and clean and it's dark and it should fade out in time for the
wedding.
We're about to go to BTS!
Oh my god, wait, I almost forgot my...
What is it?
Xiumin is letting me spray some of her perfume.
Oh yeah.
Never ending summer.
Smells like...
April spritz.
Ah, I forgot to bring mine.
Alright, we'll see you soon!
Jersey
just got our wristband I mean this is the way to do it right
Oh
my
god.
Wednesday
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
I just wanted to see a while ago
What's jim's face look like in a computer?
I'll show you
The character we've been watching I'll show you your head
I really can't believe this
Oh no, the tea is crooked
It's crooked, it's really crooked right?
Should I redo it?
Yeah
Yesterday I went to a BTS concert and it was so freaking good I had
so much fun, I've never been to a concert like that ever And that was
my first BTS concert and I literally became an ARMY the second they started performing
like they're just so talented their aura is insane i was telling bluer sauce man
yesterday when i was at the concert that how amazing they were and immediately he
was like i'm so jealous we need to take your mom so he actually booked
all of us tickets to the day two concert so we're gonna take my mom
and his mom and it should be so fun
I'm going to the gym.
YAY!
And that is the BTS concert!
Yeah!
It's okay.